Guide to the Fiametta Olschki Papers relating to Leo S. Olschki (Firm) and Olschki family members, 1904-1994
Department of Special Collections
- Wittkower, Margot. Correspondence with her son, Mario, and her daughter-in-law, Fiammetta Witt. [1987] (Box 9, Folder 8)
- Wittkower, Margot. Correspondence with her son, Mario, and her daughter-in-law, Fiammetta Witt. [1988] (Box 9, Folder 9)
- Wittkower, Margot. Correspondence with her son, Mario, and her daughter-in-law, Fiammetta Witt. [1988] (Box 9, Folder 10)
- Wittkower, Margot. Correspondence with her son, Mario, and her daughter-in-law, Fiammetta Witt. [1989] (Box 9, Folder 11)
- Wittkower, Margot. Correspondence with her son, Mario, and her daughter-in-law, Fiammetta Witt. [1990] (Box 9, Folder 12)
- Wittkower, Margot. Correspondence with her son, Mario, and her daughter-in-law, Fiammetta Witt. [1990] (Box 9, Folder 13)
- Wittkower, Margot. Correspondence with her son, Mario, and her daughter-in-law, Fiammetta Witt. [1991] (Box 9, Folder 14)
- Wittkower, Margot. Correspondence with her son, Mario, and her daughter-in-law, Fiammetta Witt. [1991] (Box 9, Folder 15)
- Wittkower, Margot. Correspondence with her son, Mario, and her daughter-in-law, Fiammetta Witt. [1992] (Box 9, Folder 16)
- Wittkower, Margot. Correspondence with her son, Mario, and her daughter-in-law, Fiammetta Witt. [1992] (Box 9, Folder 17)
- Wittkower, Margot. Correspondence with her son, Mario, and her daughter-in-law, Fiammetta Witt. [1993] (Box 9, Folder 18)
- Wittkower, Margot. Correspondence with her son, Mario, and her daughter-in-law, Fiammetta Witt. [1993] (Box 9, Folder 19)
- Wittkower, Margot. Correspondence with her son, Mario, and her daughter-in-law, Fiammetta Witt. [1994] (Box 9, Folder 20)
- Beltrame, Giancarlo. Industrialist and collector. Correspondence. 1983-1986. (Box 10, Folder 1)
- Beltrame, Giancarlo. Industrialist and collector. Correspondence. 1986-1990. (Box 10, Folder 2)
- Bircher, Martin. Scholar and author. Correspondence. 1970-78. (Box 10, Folder 3)
- Bircher, Martin. Scholar and author. Correspondence.1978-82. (Box 10, Folder 4)
- Bircher, Martin. Scholar and author. Correspondence. 1982-85. (Box 10, Folder 5)
- Bircher, Martin. Scholar and author. Correspondence. 1985-93. (Box 10, Folder 6)
- Bury, John. Scholar and collector. Correspondence. 1980-84. (Box 10, Folder 7)
- Bury, John. Scholar and collector. Correspondence. 1985-92. (Box 10, Folder 8)
- Oechslin, Werner. Scholar, author, bibliophile. Correspondence. 1976-1978. (Box 10, Folder 9)
- Oechslin, Werner. Scholar, author, bibliophile. Correspondence. 1977-84 (Box 10, Folder 10)
- Oechslin, Werner. Scholar, author, bibliophile. Correspondence. 1985-87. (Box 10, Folder 11)
- Oechslin, Werner. Scholar, author, bibliophile. Correspondence.1988-90. (Box 10, Folder 12)
- Toulmin Meoli, Rachel. Scholar, poet, university teacher. Correspondence. 1967-68. (Box 10, Folder 13)
- Toulmin Meoli, Rachel. Scholar, poet, university teacher. Correspondence. 1968-1972. (Box 10, Folder 14)
- Toulmin Meoli, Rachel. Scholar, poet, university teacher. Correspondence. 1972-1975. (Box 10, Folder 15)
- Toulmin Meoli, Rachel. Scholar, poet, university teacher. Correspondence. 1976-1984. (Box 10, Folder 16)
- Toulmin Meoli, Rachel. Scholar, poet, university teacher. Correspondence. 1985-1989. (Box 10, Folder 17)
- Toulmin Meoli, Rachel. Scholar, poet, university teacher. Correspondence. 1990-1992. (Box 10, Folder 18)
- Toulmin Meoli, Rachel. Scholar, poet, university teacher. Correspondence. 1992-1993. (Box 10, Folder 19)
- Weil, Hanna. Painter. Strauss, Rudolf (her husband). Scientist. Correspondence. 1971-1980. (Box 11, Folder 1)
- Weil, Hanna. Painter. Strauss, Rudolf (her husband). Scientist. Correspondence. 1982-1984 (Box 11, Folder 2)
- Weil, Hanna. Painter. Strauss, Rudolf (her husband). Scientist. Correspondence. 1986-1987. (Box 11, Folder 3)
- Weil, Hanna. Painter. Strauss, Rudolf (her husband). Scientist. Correspondence. 1987-1990. (Box 11, Folder 4)
- Zorzi, Alvise. Author, historian on Venice. Correspondence.1990-91 (Box 11, Folder 5)